♪♪
♪ Don't wanna be an American idiot ♪
♪ Don't want a nation under the new mania ♪
♪ And can you hear the sound of hysteria? ♪
♪ The subliminal mind-f**k America ♪
♪ Welcome to a new kind of tension ♪
♪ All across the alien nation ♪
♪ Where everything isn't meant to be okay ♪
♪ Television dreams of tomorrow ♪
♪ We're not the ones who're meant to follow ♪
♪ For that's enough to argue ♪
♪ Well maybe I'm the f****t America ♪
♪ I'm not a part of a redneck agenda ♪
♪ Now everybody do the propaganda ♪
♪ And sing along to the age of paranoia ♪
♪ Welcome to a new kind of tension ♪
♪ All across the alien nation ♪
♪ Where everything isn't meant to be okay ♪
♪ Television dreams of tomorrow ♪
♪ We're not the ones who're meant to follow ♪
♪ For that's enough to argue ♪
♪♪
♪ Don't wanna be an American idiot ♪
♪ One nation controlled by the media ♪
♪ Information Age of hysteria ♪
♪ It's calling out to idiot America ♪
♪ Welcome to a new kind of tension ♪
♪ All across the alien nation ♪
♪ Where everything isn't meant to be okay ♪
♪ Television dreams of tomorrow ♪
♪ We're not the ones who're meant to follow ♪
♪ For that's enough to argue ♪
♪♪